withoutabox.com 2006-12-06

# Withoutabox: Refund Policy

## for **Withoutabox** ® _The Network For Independents_ SM

Updated January 2006

At Without A Box, we value our customers' privacy as we would our own. This privacy policy was developed to provide you with assurance that we won't use your data in ways that we would object to other web sites using our information. The bottom line is that the information you provide to us is respected and protected. Our privacy policy covers four separate categories: The privacy of Audience Members/Observers/General Public, Filmmakers/Festival Submitters as it relates to their film information and their personal information; The privacy of Festivals, as it relates to their internal processes and their Administrators and Staffs; General privacy and security practices covering all interactions at Withoutabox, including and beyond the scope of the festival submission process. 

## CATEGORY 1: Audience Members/Observers/Film Fans/General Public

Withoutabox collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the Withoutabox service. Withoutabox also collects other profile data including but not limited to: Types of films you enjoy watching as well as other personal interests, gender, age, city, state and country you reside in and occupation in order to assist all members of in communicating with each other. User Profile information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the Withoutabox social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join Withoutabox, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network which is open to the public. Users within a personal network communicate on Withoutabox with each other through the Withoutabox service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members unless a member reveals it themselves. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, Withoutabox allows users to search for other members using first and last name, email address, film titles, festival names, and educational institutions of corporations/organizations where users may have attended or worked. From time to time, our Festival Partners may have an interest in following up with you on your festival experience should you participate at Withoutabox through one of our Festival Partner's pages or Web site. If you do choose to participate through a Festival Partner's pages or Web site then your contact information may be made available to that festival.. 

## CATEGORY 2: Filmmakers and Film Submitters

By applying to a festival, you give that festival permission to view all of the information you have provided to us on the master entry form. You also give that festival permission to share your information with whomever that festival would normally share film submission information. Without A Box does not control how a festival uses or discloses the information you authorize us to provide to it. If you are concerned, you should check with the festival to determine how it intends to use your information. We do not disclose the list of festivals to which you apply to anyone but you. We keep this information confidential whether your film is accepted or rejected. Thus, nobody will know which festivals your films were submitted to unless one of the following occurs: You tell them;The festival makes its selections public, (which public information may also become available on our site). Most festivals only make acceptances public, and do not post rejections. 

## CATEGORY 3: Festivals, their Administrators and Staffs

We do not use or disclose the lists of filmmakers who applied to your festival or have been accepted or rejected by your festival unless you make those lists public. No one except those authorized by your festival "back office administrator" will have access to your Without A Box account and the information stored there. 

## CATEGORY 4: General Use and Security for all users and members

From time to time, we may offer you additional services or opportunities, which may require the transfer of all or some of your information to other areas of our site, associated sites, or other published media. We will present matters concerning your privacy and the integrity of your data openly and in their appropriate contexts in advance of usage. You will always have the opportunity to "opt-out" of additional services or opportunities, or to close your account with us if you feel we are not acting in the furtherance of your own goals. Acceptable uses for transferring your data include: to fulfill delivery of products and services that you may order from us which may be subcontracted or fulfilled through our third-party associations and partnerships; to compile and publish current and historical data on existent film properties and film festivals, both individual and in aggregate; to publicize and promote your film or film festival to third parties that in our judgment may present significant benefits or opportunities to filmmakers or film festivals seeking larger audiences, including but not limited to agents, distributors, exhibitors, general consumers and other film festivals.We reserve the right to send you "internal messages," "instant messages," or e-mails about customer support, technical support, updates, your account in general, or any other correspondence we determine is constructive to our community or to you as our customer. However, since it is our desire for you to enjoy an "uncluttered" experience at Without A Box, we will be extremely selective in contacting you. Withoutabox also records non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. 

If Without A Box were to become owned, in whole or in part, by a third party, that third party may also determine to contact Without A Box users for the purposes of offering their other products or for informational purposes. You would be notified in advance of any such relationship and its potential effects upon this policy. In all other cases, your personal information will not be shared with third parties unless you give that third party "opt-in" permission to contact you independent of us. Without A Box has technological and operational security procedures in place to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, alteration or unintentional destruction. Our personnel who have access to the data understand the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of such information and are bound to maintain and uphold our strict Privacy Policy. We keep track of who in the company is logged on and working in the system at any given time. At some places in the site, we use "cookies" to enhance your online experience. Cookies allow our database to recognize any information associated with one of your films or your film festival, and they allow you to navigate through our site easily. All our cookies expire when you close your system. This is done so that you must login each time you enter withoutabox.com's secure areas. Most browsers now recognize when a "cookie" is offered, and permit you to refuse or accept it. Our system will not work if you turn your cookies off. They must be on.Personal information collected by Without A Box is stored and maintained in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. Other than the uses specified above, we do not share personal information with any third parties unless we believe that such action is necessary to conform to legal requirements, protect the rights of Without A Box, or enforce the Without A Box Terms of Service. Please be aware that our web sites have advertisements that are links to the web sites of our advertisers. If you click on these links you are leaving our website. While we do not share any personal information about you when you click on these links, once you leave the Without A Box environment for a partner's site, whether festival partner or corporate sponsor, the privacy policy of the partner site may be different from Without A Box's Privacy Policy. If your computer is available to others, you should remember to logout and close your browser window when you have finished your work to ensure that others cannot access your personal information. We recognize our responsibility to protect the privacy of your personal information. If you have questions or comments about the administration of your personal information, please contact us at [privacy@withoutabox.com](mailto:privacy@withoutabox.com). You may also use this address to communicate any concerns you may have regarding compliance with our Privacy Policy.We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy to adapt to our changing business, technological innovations, and the needs and expectations of our users. If we change our Policy, these changes will be posted here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we disclose it to anyone. If we make any material change concerning how your personal information is used or disclosed, then, in addition to including such revision in this Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on the Without A Box site that such changes to the Privacy Policy are going into effect and send you an e-mail notification. If you are dissatisfied with any changes in our Policy, you will have a reasonable opportunity to object or to close your account with us. You are expected to review this Agreement periodically to ensure familiarity with the most current version. If you are interested in exploring privacy issues on the Internet further please see: Electronic Privacy Information Center - focuses attention on emerging civil liberties issues. Without A Box, Inc. is a privately owned company located in Los Angeles, California.
